{
    "subject": "resource/Tommy_Davidson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Tommy Davidson",
    "human_readable": "The name of Tommy Davidson is Tommy Davidson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799033999443054,
            "question": "What is the name of Tommy Davidson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9671317934989929,
            "question": "What is the given name of Tommy Davidson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.965282142162323,
            "question": "Is Tommy Davidson known by another name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9576754570007324,
            "question": "Is 'Tommy Davidson' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7532640695571899,
            "question": "Can you give me examples of names with similar structures to 'Tommy Davidson'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6686648726463318,
            "question": "What other information do you have about Tommy Davidson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6077362895011902,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about Tommy Davidson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5962144732475281,
            "question": "Does Tommy Davidson have a different identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.029478972777724266,
            "question": "Why is it important to know someone's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.018217245116829872,
            "question": "How do names reflect a person's identity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Tommy Davidson is Tommy Davidson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6099_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is it important to know someone's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6099_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Tommy Davidson have a different identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6099_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about Tommy Davidson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6099_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6099_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the name of Tommy Davidson is indeed Tommy Davidson. All five documents mention him as Tommy Davidson, with one document even stating his full name as Thomas \"Tommy\" Davidson."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Tommy Davidson's professional career and personal background, which confirms that his name is indeed \"Tommy Davidson.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}